Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lamson, Ernest, Nov. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wray, George B., Nov. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Grand Rapids Hand Screw Co., Nov. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 3, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mcintire, Charles, Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rasor, Alpha, Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Sheats, W.N., Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Sweeney, Mary E., Nov. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hill, David Spence, Nov. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Nov. 7, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Nov. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Burnham, George, Jr., Nov. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Nov. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Nov. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Jennings, E.H., Nov. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lamson, Ernest, Nov. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lull, Herbert W., Nov. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Moore, Wilmer L., Nov. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Parrott, Hattie, Nov. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cooper, Frank Irving, Nov. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kline, L.M., Nov. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Perkins, Fellows and Hamilton, Nov. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Rasor, Alpha, Nov. 12, 1914 (Box 1)
  - Rowell, Percy E., Nov. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wilson, R.H., Nov. 13, 1914 (Box 1)
  - Bancroft, Jessie H., Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Henry, J. Earl, Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kilham, W.H., Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McConnell, H.B., Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Nov. 14, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Nov. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Richmond, Frank C., Nov. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Dr., Nov. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Waterman-Waterbury Co., Nov. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Nov. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lull, Herbert W., Nov. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCormack, A.T., Nov. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wetzel, William A., Nov. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, William A., Nov. 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ferrell, John A., Nov. 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McDonald, A.A., Nov. 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Callahan, E.B., Nov. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hill, David Spence, Nov. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCormack, A.T., Nov. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wilson, Louis N., Nov. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wray, George B., Nov. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 21, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Avery, Lewis B., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Babbitt, Ellen C., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Cady, Bertha Chapman, Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Challman, S.A., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Salley, Nathaniel Moss, Nov. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Beard, Harrington, Nov. 26, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ittner, William B., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kelsey, William B., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Naramore, F.A., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Nov. 28, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Nov. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Waterman-Waterbury Co., Nov. 29, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Courtis, S.A., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ferrell, John A., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hauer, Harvey T., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lamson, Ernest, Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Lowe, L.L., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Miller, Frank W., Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Platt, J. Mills, Dec. 1, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Naramore, F.A., Dec. 2, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 4, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Corwin, R.W., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Feagin, William F., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Preston, Mrs. J.T., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Summers, Alexander, Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Tate, W.K., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 5, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Dec. 6, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Siebert, Victor E., Dec. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Waterman-Waterbury Co., Dec. 8, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Coblentz, H.E., Dec. 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - F.A. Davis Co., Dec. 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Taylor, H.L., Dec. 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Thomas, R.H., Dec. 9, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Tate, W.K., Dec. 10, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Dec. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Foster, James H., Dec. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Summers, Alexander, Dec. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 11, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ambrose, Margaret A., Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Haskins, C., Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Linn and McCabe, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Macon County Superintendent, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Morrison, J.H.S., Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Patton, Ruby, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Teacher, Cross Roads School, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Teacher, Cross Roads School, Dec. 12, 1913 (Box 1)
  - American Sanitary Products Co, Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Babbitt, Ellen C., Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Challman, S.A., Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Gier and Dail Manufacturing Co., Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Hamrick-Tobey Co., Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Mahoney Fountain Company, Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Murdock Manufacturing and Supp, Dec. 13, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ellis, Carlos B., Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Howell, Harry, Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Linn-McCabe Co., Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Preston, Josephine, Dec. 15, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 17, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Weeks, William H., Dec. 18, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Ludlow and Peabody, Dec. 19, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Preston, Josephine, Dec. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 20, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Aspinwall, William B., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Haskins, C.A., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - McCloskey, Alice G., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Moulthrop, S.P., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Strong, Edward K., Jr., Dec. 22, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Boykin, J.C., Dec. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Claxton, P.P., Dec. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Dec. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Linn-McCabe Co., Dec. 24, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Aspinwall, William B., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Haskins, C.A., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McClain, E.L., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McElveen, W.T., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Taylor, H.L., Jan. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, S.C., Jan. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McElveen, W.T., Jan. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 14, 1913 (Box 2)
  - Kegley, E.S., Jan. 14, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McElveen, W.T., Jan. 14, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., Jan. 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Jan. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., Jan. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Grim, J.S., Jan. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Jan. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cheney, May L., Jan. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Keene, Charles H., Jan. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Love, N.N., Jan. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 21, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McNierney, A., Jan. 21, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Smith, D.S., Jan. 22, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Jan. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Jan. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Jan. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Jan. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Grim, J.G., Jan. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Jones, W.H., Jan. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Challman, S.A., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Keene, Charles H., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ocker, W.A., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Feb. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Castle, Cora Sutton, Feb. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Feb. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Love, N.N., Feb. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Nelson, E.G., Feb. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Feb. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hefferan, Mrs. W.J., Feb. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, Feb. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - U.S. Public Health Service, Feb. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Feb. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McBrien, J.L., Feb. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified, Feb. 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Burfitt, L.R. Godfrey, Feb. 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldey, Stanley, Feb. 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hobart, Louis P., Feb. 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McElveen, W.T., Feb. 11, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bryan, E.B., Feb. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Feb. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McCarnock, W.R., Feb. 14, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., Feb. 14, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, William C., Feb. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, W.F., Feb. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Feb. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Naramore, F.A., Feb. 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Perkins, Fellows and Hamilton, Feb. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Adee, John A., Feb. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Feb. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Central Commercical and Manual, Feb. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Feb. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 21, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Aspinwall, W.B., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boehm, Peter J., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Burton, E.D., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goetze, F.A., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hirdansky, Simon, Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Perkins, D.H., Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Van Rennselaer, Martha, Feb. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, William C., Feb. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Saunderson, M.A., Feb. 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Blewett, Ben, Feb. 27, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., March 2, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., March 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bogan, William J., March 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Alderman, L.R., March 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McNutt, Randolph, March 9, 1914 (Box 2)
  - American Seating Company, March 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - American Seating Company, March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Atlas School Supply Co., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Atlas School Supply Co., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Columbia School Supply Co., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Mandel Brothers, March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Co., March 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Columbia School Supply Co., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hood, C.M., March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, March 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ferrell, John A., March 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Randolph McNutt Co., March 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - American Seating Co., April 2, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Burton, E.D., April 2, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Bruce R., April 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Bruce R., April 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W.C., Jr., April 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Meredith, April 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., April 28, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 28, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, April 28, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Stechert, G.E., April 28, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, W.O., April 28, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Roach, Walter, April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Stiles, Charles W., April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Stiles, Charles W., April 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., April 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Milton Bradley and Co., April 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified, April 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Unidentified, April 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., May 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Greene, Frederick R., May 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, May 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Talbot, Mrs. C.H., May 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - G.E. Stechert and Co., May 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., May 21, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Freen, Frederick R., May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, R.R., May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McBrien, J.M., May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., May 25, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, L.D., May 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., May 29, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Oliver C. Steele Mfg. Co., June 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner of Education, June 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, William F., June 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, Dr., June 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, Dr., July 1, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ellis, Mabel Brown, July 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LaGarde, Ellen, July 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Schreuder, A.J., July 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Story, Thomas A., July 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., July 16, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cheney, C.H., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Haddon, R.W., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, W.B., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Naramore, F.A., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Packard, F.L., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Talbott, Mrs. C.H., July 18, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Aug. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Boykin, J.C., Aug. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Goldsberry, Louise D., Aug. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Aug. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Nixon, M.F., Aug. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Aug. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, Louis N., Aug. 27, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Naramore, NFN, Sept. 2, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McBrien, J.S., Sept. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Sept. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cheney, Charles H., Oct. 1, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Monroe, Paul, Oct. 1, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Oct. 1, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Oct. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Feagin, W.F., Oct. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hatch, Wallace, Oct. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - McBrien, J.L., Oct. 6, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Carroll, James E., Oct. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hanson-Bellows Co., Oct. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Jones, Martha R., Oct. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Oct. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Rider-Ericsson Engine Co., Oct. 13, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Oct. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Nicholson, M.M., Oct. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Nelson, A.H., Oct. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Dana G., Oct. 20, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ferrell, John A., Oct. 23, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Beers, Clifford W., Oct. 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, Oct. 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Rasor, Alpha, Oct. 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Nelson, A.H., Nov. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Roach, Walter W., Nov. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wray, George B., Nov. 4, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Beers, Clifford W., Nov. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Payne, Dr., Nov. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 7, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Nov. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Lee, R.E., Nov. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wray, George B., Nov. 12, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Nov. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman, Nov. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Lee, R.E., Nov. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Miller, A. E., Nov. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cobb, H.A., Nov. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Nov. 24, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Belcher A., Dec. 1, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, William B., Dec. 3, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Dec. 3, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Moultrop, S., Dec. 3, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Portis, R. Rivers, Dec. 3, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Blue, Rupert, Dec. 5, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bronson, Charles A., Dec. 8, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Burnham, W.H., Dec. 8, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, T.W., Dec. 8, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Cheney, Charles H., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Corwin, R.W., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick C., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hacker, W.A., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Steele, William L., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Dec. 10, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Blue, Rupert, Dec. 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, T.W., Dec. 15, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Howell, Harry, Dec. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, Thomas W., Dec. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Rasor, Alpha, Dec. 17, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Bruce, William C., Dec. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., Dec. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Dec. 19, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr., Dec. 22, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Mr., Dec. 26, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, D.G., Dec. 30, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Blue, Rupert C., Dec. 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Franklin, W.S., Dec. 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, Dana G., Dec. 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Stiles, O.W., Dec. 31, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1914, undated (Box 2)
  - Ferrell, John A., Jan. 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kellogg, Fanny, Jan. 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Linn, W.B., Jan. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wray, George B., Jan. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Patterson, Thomas H., Jan. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wood, Thomas D., Jan. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Jan. 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Dixon, Samuel G., Jan. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Goddard, Henry H., Jan. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Meier, Henry, Jan. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Reiche, Karl A., Jan. 21, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Jan. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kinnaman, A.J., Jan. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wray, George B., Jan. 22, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Burbank, S.M., Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Charles Scribner and Sons, Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kinnaman, A.J., Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Martin, Mrs. Atwood R., Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roemer, O.P., Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Taylor, H.L., Jan. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton. P.P., Feb. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Franklin, W.S., Feb. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Palmer, T.W., Feb. 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roemer, T.P., Feb. 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 6, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Abercrombie, John, Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Challman, S.A., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Chamberlain, A.H., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, George E., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McElhaney, Ethel F., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Odum, Howard, Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Storey, T.E., Feb. 9, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., Feb. 13, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Broady, Nancy Lee, Feb. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Guilbert and Betelle, Architects, Feb. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kinnaman, A.J., Feb. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Odum, Howard W., Feb. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wynn, W., Feb. 16, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Feb. 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Story, T.E., Feb. 18, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, R.C., Feb. 19, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hillis, Edith, Feb. 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., Feb. 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., Feb. 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McElhaney, Ethel F., Feb. 20, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Church, A.K., Feb. 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Claxton, P.P., Feb. 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - F.A. Davis and Co., Feb. 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Jones, Addison L., Feb. 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Feb. 24, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bowers, John H., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Challman, S.A., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lindsley, Louise G., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Perkins, Fellows and Hamilton, Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Storey, Thomas A., Feb. 25, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnston, R.C., Feb. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kinnaman, A.J., Feb. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Putnam, D.G., Feb. 26, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Frank H., Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hutchens, W.T., Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Journal Boston Society Medical, Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Love, Edgar L., Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wallis, R.C., Feb. 27, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Dodson, John M., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnston, R.C., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lathrop, Julia C., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCulloch, J.E., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Roemer, O.P., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Skidmore, C.H., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wallis, R.C., March 1, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., March 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., March 2, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Crozier, N.R., March 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Johnston, R.C., March 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Morgenthaler, F.S., March 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Rice Hotel, March 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Wolcott, John D., March 3, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Adcock, J.A.B., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Bracken, H.M., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Burkart, John L., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Carr, E. Arthur, March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Cosswell, W.F., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Grumbine, S.J., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Currie, Donald H., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Dowling, Oscar, March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Drake, C. St. Clair, March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Falk, Ralph, March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Frantz, A.E., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Fulton, John S., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Galloway, E.H., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Harris, H.F., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hunter, Pauli S., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hurty, J.N., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lee, S.L., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Looney, Robert N., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCormack, A.T., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Porter, Joseph Y., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Porter, K.B., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Richardson, Mark W., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Sanders, W.H., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, Morgan, March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Sumner, Guilford H., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Townsend, Joseph H., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Watson, Irving A., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Woodward, William C., March 4, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Beatty, T.B., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Biggs, Herman M., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Dalton, Charles F., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Dixon, Samuel G., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Harper, C.A., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Hayne, James A., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Heiser, Victor G., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Jepson, S.L., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kelley, Eugene R., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kingsley, Sherman C., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lillard, R.Q., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lippitt, William F., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McCampbell, E.F., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - McGurren, J.M., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Mahr, J.C., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Price, Jacob C., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Rankin, W.S., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Steiner, Ralph, March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Swarts, Gardner T., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - White, Calvin S., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Williams, Ennion G., March 5, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Snow, William F., March 7, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Brooks, Frankie, March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Corwin, R.W., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Green, Frederick R., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Ittner, William B., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Kalbach, L.A., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Frederick S., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - LeGarde, Ellen, March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Matthews, Homer D., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Robertson, A.T., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Smith, C.O., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Terman, Lewis M., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Woolcott, John D., March 8, 1915 (Box 2)
  - Broady, Nancy L., March 10, 1914 (Box 2)